♪She's a beautiful girl♪
♪إنها فتاة جميلة♪
Extra point.
نقطة إضافية.
Wang,
وانغ،
(Lanshui Lucky Welfare Lottery)
(يانصيب الرفاهية المحظوظ لانشوي)
give me a lottery ticket.
أعطني تذكرة يانصيب.
Machine selection?
اختيار آلي؟
Dad, I'm going out.
أبي، سأخرج.
Dinner's ready for you.
العشاء جاهز لك.
Is there any allowance
هل هناك أي بدل
for overtime work in your factory?
للعمل الإضافي في مصنعك؟
(Yueshi Textile Factory Residential Compound)
(مجمع سكني لمصنع يوشي للنسيج)
(Yushan Lake Park)
(حديقة بحيرة يوشان)
=Playing Go=
=لعب جو=
=Episode 13= =The Day of the Storm=
=الحلقة 13= =يوم العاصفة=
Fly higher.
حلّق أعلى.
Where are we going later?
إلى أين سنذهب لاحقًا؟
We'll go wherever you want.
سنذهب إلى أي مكان تريد.
Okay.
حسنًا.
I said it's slippery.
قلت إنه زلق.
Are you still leaving?
هل ما زلت ستغادر؟
No.
لا.
Where are we going later?
إلى أين سنذهب لاحقًا؟
Where would you like to go?
إلى أين ترغب في الذهاب؟
(The terrorists have won.)
(الإرهابيون قد فازوا.)
You're not bad.
أنت لست سيئًا.
You've been hiding your skills, huh?
كنت تخفي مهاراتك، أليس كذلك؟
One more round.
جولة أخرى.
Come on.
هيا.
Let's get married.
دعينا نتزوج.
Get married.
تزوجي.
Are you kidding me?
هل تمزح معي؟
I'm serious.
أنا جاد.
You just beat me once
لقد هزمتني مرة واحدة فقط
and you want to marry me?
وتريد الزواج مني؟
Are you convinced?
هل أنت مقتنع؟
Can't you tell I let you get away with it?
ألا تستطيع أن تدرك أنني سمحت لك بالإفلات من العقاب؟
I'm not convinced.
أنا لست مقتنعًا.
Again.
مرة أخرى.
I do.
نعم، أفعل.
I just asked her.
لقد سألتها للتو.
I wonder if I did the right thing.
أتساءل إن كنت قد فعلت الشيء الصحيح.
She didn't tell me anything.
لم تخبرني بأي شيء.
- I think you did the right thing. - Do you think I am a coward?
- أعتقد أنك فعلت الشيء الصحيح. - هل تعتقد أنني جبان؟
No.
لا.
If you take that step,
إذا اتخذت تلك الخطوة،
you're throwing in the towel.
فأنت تستسلم.
You're brave
أنت شجاع
if you don't take that step.
إذا لم تتخذ تلك الخطوة.
At least you can go on
على الأقل يمكنك الاستمرار
with your life.
في حياتك.
I'm not brave at all.
أنا لست شجاعًا على الإطلاق.
It's all because of Xia Yu's phone call.
كل هذا بسبب مكالمة شيا يو.
Only you and Xia Yu
فقط أنت وشيا يو
are good to me in this world.
تتعاملان معي بلطف في هذا العالم.
Now I don't know
الآن لا أعرف
where else to go.
إلى أين أذهب.
Just stay if you want to.
ابق إذا كنت تريد.
Have you
هل قمت
taken care of your money?
بالعناية بأموالك؟
I took some
أخذت بعض المال
for my dad's grave,
لقبر والدي،
gave some to my uncle,
وأعطيت بعضه لعمي،
and hid the rest.
وأخفيت الباقي.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
It's perfectly safe.
إنه آمن تمامًا.
I know
أعلم
it's dangerous for me to come back.
أن عودتي خطيرة.
I promise you
أعدك
I won't cause any trouble
لن أسبب أي مشاكل
or bother you again.
أو أزعجك مرة أخرى.
I'll just use the money
سأستخدم المال فقط
to open a small shop
لفتح متجر صغير
and get on with my life.
وأواصل حياتي.
Ye,
يه،
today
اليوم
may be the last time we see each other
قد تكون هذه آخر مرة نرى بعضنا فيها
in this life.
في هذه الحياة.
Can I call you that?
هل يمكنني أن أناديك بذلك؟
I wish you and...
أتمنى لك ولـ...
You and her have a good life.
أتمنى لكما حياة سعيدة.
You're rich now.
أنت غني الآن.
She won't change.
لن تتغير.
Ye,
يه،
it's all about me.
الأمر كله يتعلق بي.
Why did you want to see me?
لماذا أردت رؤيتي؟
Nothing.
لا شيء.
It's quite a good car.
إنها سيارة جيدة جدًا.
I'll be going now.
سأذهب الآن.
Mr. Cui, you're back.
سيد تسوي، لقد عدت.
Mr. Cui,
سيد تسوي،
everything's going well for us here now.
كل شيء يسير على ما يرام هنا الآن.
I'm going to pick up Director Chen.
سأذهب لأخذ المدير تشن.
As long as Director Chen is here,
طالما المدير تشن هنا،
the rich bosses will come to us.
سيأتي إلينا الرؤساء الأغنياء.
Right, how much money do we have on the books?
صحيح، كم من المال لدينا في الحسابات؟
It's long since run out.
لقد نفد منذ فترة طويلة.
Look how well we're doing here.
انظر كيف نحن نعمل بشكل جيد هنا.
I even invested money in it.
لقد استثمرت المال فيه أيضًا.
(Jingwei Go Master Academy)
(أكاديمية جينغوي لتعليم لعبة جو)
Hi, Mr. Cui and Mr. Zhang.
مرحبًا، سيد تسوي وسيد تشانغ.
Mr. Cui,
سيد تسوي،
I need to tell you something.
أحتاج أن أخبرك بشيء.
Don't ever ask these kids to come here again.
لا تطلب من هؤلاء الأطفال القدوم هنا مرة أخرى.
The noise will disturb Director Chen and the others from discussing business.
الضوضاء ستزعج المدير تشن والآخرين من مناقشة الأعمال.
Mr. Cui,
سيد تسوي،
we are running this master class
نحن ندير هذه الدورة المتقدمة
as a platform
كمنصة
to make some money,
لجني بعض المال،
not as a real educational endeavor.
وليس كمشروع تعليمي حقيقي.
You knew this before, didn't you?
كنت تعرف هذا من قبل، أليس كذلك؟
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
I have to go now.
يجب أن أذهب الآن.
Mr. Cui,
سيد تسوي،
my mom said I must pay you back the fees.
قالت أمي أنه يجب علي أن أعيد لك الرسوم.
As long as you learn go well,
طالما أنك تتعلم لعبة جو جيدًا،
I'll be happy.
سأكون سعيدًا.
Have you improved lately?
هل تحسنت مؤخرًا؟
Test me and you will know it.
اختبرني وستعرف ذلك.
Mr. Cui,
سيد تسوي،
did I make such a good move?
هل قمت بحركة جيدة؟
It's my turn.
حان دوري.
I thought I'd made a good move
ظننت أنني قمت بخطوة جيدة
that took you so long to think about.
التي استغرقت وقتًا طويلاً للتفكير فيها.
You did make a good move.
لقد قمت بخطوة جيدة بالفعل.
I was thinking about the next move.
كنت أفكر في الخطوة التالية.
(Buy used cars at high prices)
(شراء السيارات المستعملة بأسعار مرتفعة)
(Information Desk)
(مكتب المعلومات)
Here, this price.
هنا، هذا السعر.
That's too much of a markdown.
هذا تخفيض كبير جدًا.
That's the price.
هذا هو السعر.
This car has been modified.
تم تعديل هذه السيارة.
Think about selling it or not.
فكر في بيعه أم لا.
Come and get the paperwork done with me.
تعال وأنجز الأوراق معي.
Come on.
هيا.
If you need money in a hurry,
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى المال بسرعة،
I can recommend a place.
أستطيع أن أوصي بمكان.
Go to this place.
اذهب إلى هذا المكان.
(Need money in a hurry? Call us. Manager: Liu Qinglong)
(تحتاج إلى المال بسرعة؟ اتصل بنا. المدير: ليو تشينغ لونغ)
(Yijia Department Store)
(متجر ييجيا)
(Laoshi Dumpling Restaurant)
(مطعم لاوشي للزلابية)
This kid
هذا الطفل
has changed after a trip. Look.
تغير بعد الرحلة. انظر.
He doesn't even play video games anymore.
لم يعد يلعب ألعاب الفيديو.
Good boy.
ولد جيد.
Yan,
يان،
do you want to take a break first?
هل تريد أن تأخذ استراحة أولاً؟
You haven't fed your fish yet, have you?
لم تطعم أسماكك بعد، أليس كذلك؟
Mom,
أمي،
help me feed them.
ساعديني في إطعامهم.
(Mingyu Foreign Trade, Join Us)
(التجارة الخارجية مينغيو، انضم إلينا)
Why are you still up?
لماذا ما زلت مستيقظًا؟
What are you calculating?
ماذا تحسب؟
I'm calculating for the master class.
أحسب من أجل الصف الرئيسي.
Tell me the truth.
أخبرني الحقيقة.
How much will it take
كم سيكلف
to treat Yan's disease?
لعلاج مرض يان؟
You stay out of this.
ابق خارج هذا.
How can I stay out of it?
كيف يمكنني أن أبقى خارج هذا؟
I want to go to work tomorrow.
أريد أن أذهب إلى العمل غدًا.
Your job is to take care of Yan.
وظيفتك هي الاعتناء بـ يان.
Yan's disease can be cured.
مرض يان يمكن علاجه.
That's good news.
هذه أخبار جيدة.
Stop frowning all the time, will you?
توقف عن العبوس طوال الوقت، أليس كذلك؟
Go to bed.
اذهب إلى الفراش.
Dad,
أبي،
where is your car?
أين سيارتك؟
There's a little problem.
هناك مشكلة صغيرة.
I sent it for repair.
أرسلتها للإصلاح.
Come on.
هيا.
Sit properly.
اجلس بشكل صحيح.
Okay.
حسنًا.
Be careful.
كن حذرًا.
How may I address you?
كيف يمكنني مخاطبتك؟
My surname is Cui.
لقبي هو تسوي.
What's your business?
ما هو عملك؟
I'm a teacher.
أنا معلم.
I'm running a class.
أدير صفًا دراسيًا.
It's my first time here.
هذه أول مرة لي هنا.
I'll give you a lower interest rate.
سأعطيك معدل فائدة أقل.
How much do you want to borrow?
كم تريد أن تقترض؟
I'd like to borrow 800,000 yuan.
أود أن أقترض 800,000 يوان.
Let's go and take a look.
لنذهب ونلقي نظرة.
What to look at?
ماذا ننظر؟
Look at what you're going to use as collateral.
انظر إلى ما ستستخدمه كضمان.
You can't just borrow 800,000 yuan as you wish, right?
لا يمكنك فقط اقتراض 800,000 يوان كما تشاء، صحيح؟
800,000 yuan
800,000 يوان
is a lot of money.
هو مبلغ كبير من المال.
I have to look at where you live
يجب أن أنظر إلى مكان إقامتك
and where your class is.
وأين صفك الدراسي.
Long.
لونغ.
Mr. Liu.
السيد ليو.
Sit down.
اجلس.
I've got everything.
لدي كل شيء.
I'll give you my cannery as collateral
سأعطيك مصنع التعليب الخاص بي كضمان
to borrow another half a million.
لاقتراض نصف مليون آخر.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
I've got all the money ready for you.
لدي كل المال جاهز لك.
Thank you.
شكراً لك.
I'll proceed with the formalities.
سأتابع الإجراءات.
You'll get your money then.
ستحصل على المال حينها.
Sure, thank you.
بالتأكيد، شكراً لك.
Is the amount correct?
هل المبلغ صحيح؟
Sign the contract.
وقع العقد.
Hey,
مهلاً،
what are you looking at?
ماذا تنظر؟
Are you going to borrow the money or not?
هل ستقترض المال أم لا؟
What are you doing here?
ماذا تفعل هنا؟
I came to see the view.
جئت لأرى المنظر.
Well, when I asked you about that question in the Internet cafe,
حسنًا، عندما سألتك عن ذلك السؤال في مقهى الإنترنت،
did you say yes?
هل قلت نعم؟
Who knows if you were serious?
من يعلم إذا كنت جادًا؟
Of course I was serious.
بالطبع كنت جادًا.
What kind of person says that when they're blowing people's heads off?
أي نوع من الأشخاص يقول ذلك عندما يكون مشغولًا بتفجير رؤوس الناس؟
Look.
انظر.
No.
لا.
I'm really serious.
أنا جاد حقًا.
So tell me how serious you are.
إذاً أخبرني كم أنت جاد.
I've got it all figured out.
لقد خططت لكل شيء.
You quit your job.
لقد تركت وظيفتك.
I
أنا
will open an Internet cafe.
سأفتح مقهى إنترنت.
We'll make money when people come.
سنكسب المال عندما يأتي الناس.
If no one comes,
إذا لم يأت أحد،
we'll play hard
سنلعب بجد
and have fun.
ونستمتع.
All you do is play.
كل ما تفعله هو اللعب.
I'm not leaving the factory.
لن أترك المصنع.
If you really want to be with me,
إذا كنت تريد حقًا أن تكون معي،
get a proper job.
احصل على وظيفة مناسبة.
Is opening an Internet cafe not proper?
هل فتح مقهى إنترنت ليس مناسبًا؟
Have you received the letter I sent you?
هل تلقيت الرسالة التي أرسلتها لك؟
Letter?
رسالة؟
Did you send me a letter?
هل أرسلت لي رسالة؟
Hello.
مرحبا.
What's wrong?
ما الأمر؟
Something's wrong with the factory's goods. I have to go now.
هناك خطأ في بضائع المصنع. يجب أن أذهب الآن.
(Property Ownership Certificate)
شهادة ملكية العقار
(Bless your son. From Handkerchief)
(بارك ابنك. من منديل)
- We've lost all our hard-earned money. - You must give us an explanation.
- لقد فقدنا كل أموالنا التي كسبناها بشق الأنفس. - يجب أن تعطينا تفسيرًا.
What's the solution?
ما هو الحل؟
Li.
لي.
Li,
لي,
aren't you usually a reliable person?
أليس من المعتاد أنك شخص موثوق؟
Why did you make a mistake when it mattered?
لماذا ارتكبت خطأ عندما كان الأمر مهمًا؟
Why this batch?
لماذا هذه الدفعة؟
If this batch is ruined,
إذا تلفت هذه الدفعة،
our factory will be ruined.
مصنعنا سيتدمر.
You're driving us to death.
أنت تقودنا إلى الهلاك.
If the factory is ruined,
إذا تدمر المصنع،
you'll be a sinner.
ستكون مذنبًا.
It's my fault. Don't blame Li.
إنه خطأي. لا تلوم لي.
We've all become sinners.
لقد أصبحنا جميعًا مذنبين.
You,
أنت،
your dad tricked your mum by gambling with the factory's money.
والدك خدع والدتك بالمقامرة بأموال المصنع.
- We've raised money for you once. - Yes.
- لقد جمعنا المال من أجلك مرة واحدة. - نعم.
Why did the factory
لماذا كان على المصنع
have to deal with your family?
أن يتعامل مع عائلتك؟
Calm down, everyone.
اهدأوا جميعًا.
Pay us back!
ادفعوا لنا!
Feng, you're just in time.
فينغ، وصلت في الوقت المناسب.
I was just looking for you.
كنت أبحث عنك.
(Yueshi Textile Factory Is My Home) Does the factory
(مصنع النسيج يوشي هو منزلي) هل المصنع
(Development Depends On All) want everyone
(التنمية تعتمد على الجميع) يريد من الجميع
to pay for the damages?
أن يدفعوا ثمن الأضرار؟
Does it?
هل هذا صحيح؟
We don't have any money.
ليس لدينا أي مال.
Why is that?
لماذا هذا؟
We don't have money.
ليس لدينا مال.
- Listen to me, everyone. - We don't have money.
- استمعوا إلي، جميعًا. - ليس لدينا مال.
We have two family members working in the factory.
لدينا اثنان من أفراد الأسرة يعملون في المصنع.
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
Give us an idea.
أعطنا فكرة.
We must solve it.
يجب أن نحلها.
How else can we live?
كيف يمكننا العيش بطريقة أخرى؟
How can we live?
كيف يمكننا العيش؟
Where else can we make a living?
أين يمكننا أن نكسب رزقنا؟
Give us an explanation.
أعطنا تفسيرًا.
I'll give you all a satisfactory answer.
سأعطيكم جميعًا إجابة مرضية.
Li.
لي.
- Get down.
- انزل.
Don't jump.
لا تقفز.
- Li. - No.
- لي. - لا.
- Get down.
- انزل.
- Get down now.
- انزل الآن.
Get down now.
انزل الآن.
Li,
لي،
get down first.
انزل أولاً.
I'm sure we'll work something out.
أنا متأكد أننا سنتوصل إلى حل.
It's really not your fault this time.
هذه المرة ليست غلطتك حقاً.
- It's my responsibility. - I shouldn't have
- إنها مسؤوليتي. - لم يكن يجب أن
left my duty.
أترك واجبي.
I'm responsible for it.
أنا مسؤول عن ذلك.
It's all my fault.
إنه خطأي بالكامل.
Uncle Song has been working in this factory all his life.
العم سونغ كان يعمل في هذا المصنع طوال حياته.
He'll retire in a year.
سيتقاعد بعد عام.
Wei's whole family are factory workers.
عائلة وي بأكملها تعمل في المصنع.
And Shen,
وشن،
Xiao,
شياو،
Li.
لي.
Li's husband was laid off a long time ago.
زوج لي تم تسريحه منذ وقت طويل.
She's raising a family on her own.
هي تربي الأسرة بمفردها.
It was actually my shift that day,
كان في الواقع نوبتي في ذلك اليوم،
but I didn't even notice that the machine was acting up.
لكنني لم ألاحظ حتى أن الآلة كانت تتصرف بشكل غريب.
This batch is the last hope of the factory.
هذه الدفعة هي الأمل الأخير للمصنع.
If the factory is closed down,
إذا تم إغلاق المصنع،
what will happen to everyone?
ماذا سيحدث للجميع؟
I'm the one who should die.
أنا من يجب أن يموت.
Does it mean the factory won't have to close down
هل يعني ذلك أن المصنع لن يضطر إلى الإغلاق
if we compensate for that money?
إذا قمنا بتعويض تلك الأموال؟
I have money.
لدي المال.
I called you
اتصلت بك
on my birthday
في عيد ميلادي
and said I'd sent you a card
وقلت إنني أرسلت لك بطاقة
and the stuff inside was left for you.
والأشياء داخلها تركت لك.
Do you remember?
هل تتذكر؟
That's a card from the depository at the train station.
هذه بطاقة من المستودع في محطة القطار.
There's money in it.
يوجد مال بداخلها.
It's enough to save your factory.
إنه يكفي لإنقاذ مصنعك.
It's all because I called you.
كل هذا لأنني اتصلت بك.
I should take care of it.
يجب أن أعتني بالأمر.
I sent it by registered mail.
أرسلتها بالبريد المسجل.
It should be here by now.
يجب أن تكون قد وصلت الآن.
(Mr. Cui)
(السيد تسوي)
I have something to do and have to go right now.
لدي شيء يجب أن أفعله ويجب أن أذهب الآن.
Xia Yu,
شيا يو،
believe me.
صدقني.
Now, you go back and see if the registered letter has arrived.
الآن، عد وتحقق إذا وصلت الرسالة المسجلة.
I'll meet you later.
سألتقي بك لاحقًا.
Okay?
حسنًا؟
All right, I'll see you later.
حسنًا، سأراك لاحقًا.
Xia Yu,
شيا يو،
your registered mail.
بريدك المسجل.
Uncle Xia.
عمي شيا.
Is your daughter home?
هل ابنتك في المنزل؟
There's registered mail for her.
هناك بريد مسجل لها.
It needs to be signed for by the recipient.
يجب أن يتم التوقيع عليه من قبل المستلم.
You have so many rules when you come to my house.
لديك الكثير من القواعد عندما تأتي إلى منزلي.
Give me the pen.
أعطني القلم.
Okay, bye.
حسنًا، وداعًا.
Anything else?
هل هناك شيء آخر؟
Long.
طويل.
I'll definitely pay you back.
سأرد لك المال بالتأكيد.
Can you please
هل يمكنك من فضلك
give me a few more days?
أعطني بضعة أيام إضافية؟
Xia,
شيا،
I'll give you a chance.
سأعطيك فرصة.
You've got to fight for yourself.
عليك أن تقاتل من أجل نفسك.
Ten seconds counts as a day.
عشر ثواني تُحسب كيوم.
Let's see how long you can hold your breath.
دعنا نرى كم من الوقت يمكنك أن تحبس أنفاسك.
After we split up,
بعد أن افترقنا،
I took him to Hong Kong, China.
أخذته إلى هونغ كونغ، الصين.
He's been diagnosed
تم تشخيصه
as not having amyotrophic lateral sclerosis.
بعدم إصابته بالتصلب الجانبي الضموري.
I've accepted everything in the past,
لقد قبلت كل شيء في الماضي،
but now it gives me hope.
لكن الآن يمنحني الأمل.
Isn't it funny?
أليس هذا مضحكًا؟
Sometimes, hope
أحيانًا، الأمل
is worse than despair.
أسوأ من اليأس.
That's what I wanted to talk to you about
هذا ما أردت التحدث معك عنه
earlier.
في وقت سابق.
When I was in Hong Kong, China,
عندما كنت في هونغ كونغ، الصين،
you were the first person
كنت أول شخص
I could think of to help me.
يمكنني التفكير فيه ليساعدني.
But when I saw you,
لكن عندما رأيتك،
I couldn't say anything.
لم أستطع قول أي شيء.
I really,
أنا حقًا،
really have no choice.
حقًا ليس لدي خيار.
I really can't come up with that much money.
حقًا لا أستطيع توفير هذا القدر من المال.
How much do you want?
كم تريد؟
800,000 yuan.
800,000 يوان.
Please help me out.
أرجوك ساعدني.
You've got a problem?
هل لديك مشكلة؟
It's Xia Yu.
إنه شيا يو.
Something's happened to Xia Yu's factory.
حدث شيء ما لمصنع شيا يو.
She's responsible.
هي المسؤولة.
Without this money,
بدون هذا المال،
the factory could be closed down.
قد يتم إغلاق المصنع.
I've seen it before.
لقد رأيته من قبل.
It can really drive someone to death.
يمكن أن يدفع شخصًا إلى الموت حقًا.
Her factory?
مصنعها؟
What's her factory got to do with you?
ما علاقة مصنعها بك؟
For her factory,
من أجل مصنعها،
a bunch of people you don't know,
مجموعة من الأشخاص الذين لا تعرفهم،
you're willing to help them rather than me.
أنت مستعد لمساعدتهم بدلاً من مساعدتي.
That's my son.
هذا ابني.
Your pendant is still around his neck.
قلادتك لا تزال حول عنقه.
Ye.
نعم.
Don't call me that.
لا تناديني بذلك.
What's our relationship?
ما هي علاقتنا؟
I saved your life.
لقد أنقذت حياتك.
You saved my life too.
لقد أنقذت حياتي أيضًا.
We're buddies through life and death.
نحن أصدقاء في الحياة والموت.
You'd rather help them?
تفضل مساعدتهم؟
You haven't been through it.
أنت لم تمر بهذا.
Whenever there's an accident at the factory,
كلما حدث حادث في المصنع،
everyone in the factory suffers.
يعاني الجميع في المصنع.
I don't want to see them lose their lives,
لا أريد أن أراهم يفقدون حياتهم،
and I don't want
ولا أريد
this to force Xia Yu to lose her life.
أن يجبر هذا شيا يو على فقدان حياتها.
I can't
لا أستطيع
stay out of this.
أن أبقى بعيداً عن هذا.
You went gambling again?
هل ذهبت للمقامرة مرة أخرى؟
Where is my letter?
أين رسالتي؟
Where's your passbook?
أين دفتر حسابك؟
What do you need the passbook for?
لماذا تحتاج دفتر الحساب؟
Where's the thing inside?
أين الشيء الموجود بالداخل؟
I asked you where you keep your passbook.
سألتك أين تحتفظ بدفتر الحساب الخاص بك.
You don't care whether I live or die.
أنت لا تهتم إذا كنت أعيش أو أموت.
You're guarding me like a thief.
أنت تحرسني مثل اللص.
Give me your passbook!
أعطني دفتر الحساب الخاص بك!
Give me the thing inside!
أعطني الشيء الموجود بالداخل!
Give me the passbook and I'll give you the stuff.
أعطني دفتر الحساب وسأعطيك الأشياء.
What did you store at the train station?
ماذا خزنت في محطة القطار؟
Boss, one hundred more.
رئيس، مئة أخرى.
Sir,
سيدي،
you've scraped everything I have here.
لقد أخذت كل ما لدي هنا.
How about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
I'll cash these out
سأصرف هذه
for you first.
لك أولاً.
The total is 85 yuan.
المجموع هو 85 يوان.
Sir, there are slot machines in there.
سيدي، هناك آلات القمار في الداخل.
Would you like to try?
هل ترغب في المحاولة؟
Why didn't you watch out?
لماذا لم تنتبه؟
Look at you.
انظر إليك.
Why did you fall again?
لماذا سقطت مرة أخرى؟
This side. Be careful.
من هذا الجانب. كن حذراً.
Come on. Stretch your hand back.
هيا. مد يدك للخلف.
Ye, you're back just in time.
يه، عدت في الوقت المناسب.
Give Yan a bath.
أعط يان حماماً.
The kid hasn't even had his cast removed yet
الطفل لم يزل الجبيرة بعد
and he fell down again.
وسقط مرة أخرى.
Come on.
هيا.
Come on, be careful.
هيا، كن حذراً.
Where is Shuhua?
أين شو هوا؟
She went out this afternoon.
خرجت بعد ظهر اليوم.
Go on, go and take a bath with your dad.
هيا، اذهب وخذ حماماً مع والدك.
I'll get you some clean clothes.
سأحضر لك بعض الملابس النظيفة.
Ye,
يه،
the washing machine seems to be broken.
يبدو أن الغسالة معطلة.
Come and have a look later.
تعال وألقِ نظرة لاحقًا.
Yan,
يان،
why were you so careless
لماذا كنت مهملًا جدًا
and fell down again?
وسقطت مرة أخرى؟
Is there something wrong
هل هناك خطب ما
with your leg?
في ساقك؟
Dad,
أبي،
I'll never
لن أعود أبدًا
play video games again.
للعب ألعاب الفيديو مرة أخرى.
What's wrong with you?
ما خطبك؟
I want to spend all my time
أريد أن أقضي كل وقتي
learning Go with you.
في تعلم لعبة جو معك.
Teach me how to play Go.
علمني كيف ألعب جو.
I want to make up for all the time
أريد أن أعوض كل الوقت
I've wasted.
الذي أضعته.
I know all about it.
أنا أعرف كل شيء عن ذلك.
I won't be able
لن أتمكن
to stand up later.
من الوقوف لاحقًا.
I don't have to stand to play Go.
لا يجب أن أقف لألعب جو.
Dad,
أبي،
I'm ready for it.
أنا مستعد لذلك.
Hello, Dr. Lin.
مرحباً، دكتور لين.
I'm Cui Yangao's parent.
أنا والد تشوي يانغاو.
I'm not considering the option you mentioned.
أنا لا أفكر في الخيار الذي ذكرته.
Money is not an issue.
المال ليس مشكلة.
I want the best.
أريد الأفضل.
(Property Ownership Certificate)
(شهادة ملكية العقار)